《反恐24小时》前情提要
Previously on 24.
司法部正在调查乔纳斯·霍格斯
The justice department is investigating
的汽车炸弹的事
The Jonas Hodges car bombing.
我告诉过你我改变主意了
I changed my mind.
我没有转账
I didn't transfer the funds.
没给他酬劳  他为什么还对霍奇斯下手呢
Why would he go ahead and kill Hodges if he wasn't paid?!
这正合你意啊  对吧
Because it's what you wanted, am I right?
杰克  我破解了托尼的定位数据
Jack, I unlocked Tony's location data.
好  我们看到他了
Okay, we've got him.
毒气罐在哪里
Where's the canister?!
你不告诉我  我不会停手
I am not going to stop until you tell me where it is.
-杰克  -没事没事
- Jack. - It's all right, it's all right.
你该打一针了
You need to give yourself a shot.
20分钟前打过了
I already did 20 minutes ago.
没用
It's not working.
你是回家吗
You heading home?
我们也是
Us, too.
我是鲍尔
This is Bauer.
我正把链接发到你手机上
I'm sending a link to your phone.
有样东西你需要看一看
It's something I think you should see.
你女儿正在我们的控制之中
Your daughter's in the company of our operatives.
把这条线连到你耳机上  让它一直开着
Put this call on your earpiece and keep the line open.
我要监听你说的每句话
I'm gonna be listening to everything you say.
你得帮助托尼·阿尔梅达脱身
You will help Tony Almeida escape
不然我的人会杀了你女儿
Or my people will murder your daughter.
以下情节发生在凌晨6点至7点间
The following takes place between 6 a.m. and 7 a.m.
好的
Okay.
谢谢
Thank you.
司法部副部长在等你  女士
The deputy attorney general is ready for you, ma'am.
已启动网真电话会议
Telepresence call is initiated.
网络安全  请讲吧
Network is secure. Go ahead.
早上好  泰勒女士
Good morning, Ms. Taylor.
谢谢你抽空来接受这次调查
Thank you for giving up your time for this investigation.
我应该做的
Of course.
这是司法部的罗林斯夫人和霍克先生
Mrs. Rollins and Mr. Hock are from the justice department.
他们会对你进行提问
They'll be conducting your interview.
接下来是
Let the record show that this is to be the testimony
白宫首席顾问奥利维亚·泰勒关于
Of Olivia Taylor, acting white house chief of staff
联邦证人乔纳斯·霍奇斯谋杀一案的证词
Regarding the homicide of federal witness Jonas Hodges.
我出席是为了确保调查的严谨
Let it also show that I'm present to ensure that
保护泰勒女士
Strict protocols be followed for Ms. Taylor's protection.
我为什么需要保护
Why would I need protecting?
用词不准确
A poor choice of words.
只是这样  对你的询问仅是例行公事
I merely meant that, uh, your questioning is just a formality.
我们得对所有知道霍奇斯出事前行踪的人
We have to go through everyone who had knowledge of
进行调查
Hodges' whereabouts up until the time of the car bombing.
明白了
I see.
罗林斯夫人  到你了
Mrs. rollins, you have the floor.
开始吧
Let's begin.
我让奥利维亚来参加这次通报会
I wanted olivia in this briefing.
-她在哪里  -抱歉  女士
- Where is she? - I'm sorry, ma'am,
她正跟司法部副部长在一起
But she's tied up with the deputy a.g.
接受霍奇斯谋杀一案的调查
And investigators looking into the Hodges murder.
他们查到谁泄露了霍奇斯所在地点了吗
Have they made any progress on who leaked Hodges' location?
还没有
Not yet.
但他们认为知道霍奇斯还活着
But they agree that the list of people
待在调查局的人很少
Who knew Hodges was alive and at FBI is short.
泄密人应该是内部人员
The leak had to come from inside.
早上好  各位
Good morning, everyone.
早上好  总统阁下
Morning, madam president.
总统阁下
Madam president.
请坐
Please take your seats.
我知道大家都很困顿
I realize that we are all in dire need of sleep.
但让各位及时了解
But I felt that it was vital to bring you all up to speed
过去几小时发生的事情
On the events of the past few hours
以及即将发生更大的危机  刻不容缓
And a greater crisis we face on the horizon.
不到30分钟前  调查局成功找到
Less than 30 minutes ago, the FBI managed to recover
最后一罐生化武器
The last canister of the bioweapon.
但恐怕危险还未解除
But I'm afraid that the danger is far from over.
在乔纳斯·霍奇斯被杀前  他说
Before his death, Jonas Hodges told us
还有其他势力也参与了
That there were other parties involved with him
生化武器的研制
In the creation of this bioweapon--
一些极为隐蔽  既有权势
A highly secret and extremely powerful group
的私人军工企业
Of private military firms
勾结起来破坏我们国家的政府
Collaborating to undermine the government of this country.
不好意思  总统阁下
Excuse me, madam president.
我们说的是哪些军工企业
But which military firms are we talking about?
我们不知道  上将
We don't know, admiral.
霍奇斯没有透露这些公司
Hodges gave us no names or idea
的名字或其他信息
Of which companies are involved.
但不管他们是谁
But whoever they are,
他们都是实实在在的威胁
They represent a very real and ongoing threat.
目前我们没有可靠情报
Now, we don't have much actionable intelligence at this point.
联邦调查局已经拘押了前反恐组成员
However, the FBI has apprehended former CTU operative
托尼·阿尔梅达
Tony almeida.
他是这次阴谋的关键人物
He is a key figure in this plot,
我们希望能通过他
And someone we hope will be able to help us
找到这些人
Uncover who these people are.
沃克探员  我是布拉沃三号空援组
Agent Walker, this is air support Bravo Three.
我们已就位  你们的护卫队在视线范围
We're in position. Your convoy is in sight.
收到  布拉沃三号
Roger that, Bravo Three.
警方会调控交通
Metro will be controlling traffic
在市区建立安全通道
And setting up a secure corridor through the downtown area.
我们会带托尼·阿尔梅达
We'll be bringing Almeida into headquarters
从西大门进入总部
Through the west entrance.
鲍尔先生  是时候了
It's almost time, Mr. Bauer.
跟你一起的护卫队快下I-70洲际公路了
The convoy you're traveling with is about to get off on the I-70.
在进入市区前你必须得行动
You need to break off before you reach the downtown exit
否则就没那么容易帮托尼逃走了
Or you'll lose your chance to facilitate an escape for Tony.
为了你女儿好
For your daughter's sake,
你不想这样的
You don't want that to happen.
现在好好给我听着
Now listen carefully.
你得控制这辆车
You'll need to commandeer the van
开到约四英里外的塔夫特大街路口
And peel onto the taft street exit in about four miles.
到了后我再说怎么做
I'll direct you further once you've managed that.
记住  我手下的人正看着你女儿
Remember, my operatives are with your daughter.
事实上  她的一举一动我都清楚
In fact, I'm looking at her right now.
别想逞英雄
So don't try to be a hero.
怎么了
Something wrong?
感觉飞机要满员了
It's just starting to look like the flight is gonna be full,
我只能做下一班
And I'm on standby.
不不  你肯定能登机的
No, no, you're gonna get on.
昨天飞机差点相撞的事情
I mean, there have to be some people that are too spooked
肯定有人心有余悸不敢来了
To fly after those planes went down yesterday.
鲍勃
Bob.
提那事干嘛
Did you have to bring that up?
就是说说
I'm just saying.
他们做了预防措施
Look, I think it makes us safer.
会让我们更安心
They're gonna take extra precautions.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
这些是你的行李吗
Are those yours?
是的
Yeah, that's right.
能麻烦挪一下吗  为我妈妈腾个地方
Would you mind, so my mother could sit down, please?
当然
Oh, sure.
谢谢
Thanks.
你流血了
Oh, you're bleeding.
什么
What?
你脖子上有一个抓伤
You have a scratch on your neck.
亲爱的
Honey.
是不是你下出租时
Oh, that must have happened
碰到了门呀
When the door hit you getting out of the cab.
哦
Oh, well, I'll just, uh,
我去报刊亭那边
I'll-i'll go to the newsstand
看看有没有创可贴卖
And see if they have some band-aids.
怎么了
What is it?
我有点担心
I'm getting worried.
早晚特勤局探员尸体
It's only a matter of time before
会被发现
That FBI agent's body is discovered.
鲍尔的女儿好像在怀疑了
And I think Bauer's daughter is getting suspicious.
我给鲍尔限定的时间交出托尼
Look, I gave Bauer a short window to deliver Tony to me.
不会很久的
Won't be long.
好了我会通知你
Just stand by until you hear from me.
如果鲍尔的女儿在那之前发现我们了呢
And what if kim bauer makes us before then?
你不能冒险被抓
You can't allow yourselves to be taken.
你知道怎么做的
Do what you have to do.
沃克探员  看一下你的耳机
Agent walker, let me see your comm unit.
我要调试一下频率
I want to adjust this frequency.
我的被干扰了
It's interrupting mine.
谢谢
Thanks.
别动
Don't move.
-别动  -杰克
- Don't move! - Jack.
司机  继续开车
Driver, just keep going
不会伤你们的
And no one gets hurt.
你们俩  慢慢的把抢拿出来
Both of you, I want you to slowly
放在地上
Draw your weapons, put them on the floor
踢到我这边来
And slide them to me.
-杰克  -快点
- Jack  - Do it!
不要再为难我了
Don't make this any harder than it already is.
把抢给我  否则我就杀了他
Give me your weapon or I will kill him.
杰克  你不会下手的
Come on, Jack, you're not gonna kill anyone.
快把抢给我
Give me your weapon! now!
司机  把手拷在方向盘上
Driver, I want you to handcuff
上下都拷好
Yourself to the steering wheel, over and under.
快点
Do it now.
准备好下高速路
You're gonna exit the freeway when I tell you.
在那之前  保持现速
Until then, I want you to maintain speed.
现在
Now!
沃克探员  怎么了  沃克探员
Agent Walker, what's happening? agent Walker?
押送罪犯的车脱离了警卫车队
Comm, the prisoner transport has split from the convoy.
蕾妮  我是詹尼斯  听到请回话
Renee, it's Janis, do you read me?
蕾妮
Renee!
听到请回话
Are you reading me?
沃克探员  什么情况
Agent Walker, what's your 20?
沃克探员  请回答
Agent Walker, please respond.
杰克  为什么这么做
Jack, why?
我女儿在他们手里
They've got my daughter.
不可能的
That's not possible.
我按你的要求派弗兰克探员保护她
I deployed agent Franks to watch over her, like you asked.
弗兰克探员已经死了
Agent franks is dead.
这些人是托尼一伙的
The people that are working with tony
金在他们的监视之下
Have operatives with kim right now.
-杰克  -他们要我帮托尼逃跑
- Jack! - They threatened to kill her
否则就杀了她
If I don't break him out.
杰克  够了
Jack, that's enough!
你这个贱人
You son of a bitch.
我们下高速了  现在呢
Okay, we're on taft. what now?
你会看见康涅狄格隧道的入口
You'll see the entrance to the Connecticut avenue tunnel.
走北边的车道
Take the north lane.
继续沿街行驶
Continue down this street.
走北边进隧道
Go towards the tunnel, north.
空中监视  还看得到嫌犯的车吗
Aerial bravo three, do you still have a visual?
是的
Affirmative.
剩下的车队
The follow vehicles in the convoy
会在下个出口下高速
Are getting off at the next exit,
我们会继续追踪
And will be doubling back.
我们在卫星追踪嫌犯的车
We've got prisoner transport on satellite.
他们冲着哈德森去了
They're heading west on hudson.
等下
Wait.
他们进入康涅狄格隧道入口了
They're pulling into the connecticut avenue tunnel.
我看不到
I'm losing visual.
重复  看不到了
Repeat, I am losing visual.
连线发射器
Pull up the transponder locators.
我们在隧道里了
Okay, we're in the tunnel.
我在25英里处
You'll see me parked in
的紧急停车道上
The emergency lane about a quarter mile in.
你停在那辆SUV后面
Okay, I want you to pull behind that suv.
杰克  我能理解你的原因
Jack, please. I understand your reasons,
但是你不能这么做
But you can't do this.
不  我不能让金出于危险之中  解开托尼
No, what I can't do is risk kim's life. uncuff Tony.
给我钥匙
Give me the keys.
拷住她  我来管这个
Cuff her. I'll take him.
他们摄像监视着金
They have a camera on kim.
我不相信托尼会放了她
I don't trust Tony to let her go.
求你了
Please, I'm begging you,
竭尽所能去救她  求你了
Do whatever you have to to save her, please.
杰克
Jack.
枪给我
The gun.
把自己铐上
Cuff yourself.
快
Come on.
你把鲍尔带来干什么
What are you bringing Bauer for?
托尼  我听从了你们的一切指示
Tony, I've done everything you've asked.
放了金
Just let Kim go.
-放了她  -上车
- Let her go! - Get in the car.
托尼  你想干什么
So what are you doing, Tony?
我们不需要人质  尤其是他
We don't need a hostage, okay-- specially not him.
把他毙了  我们远走高飞
Shoot him already and let's get out of here.
卡拉  你真是没有远见
You're not seeing the big picture, Cara.
你们组织将能发射生化武器
Your people are gonna be able to launch the biological attacks--
就和原计划一样
Just as they originally planned.
怎么做
How?
我们已经丢了毒气罐
We lost the canister.
病原体已经不在我们手中
We don't have the pathogen anymore.
我们有杰克就够
We have Jack.
病原体在他的血液里
The pathogen's in his blood,
就在他的器官里
It's in his organs.
我们可以从他体内摄取所有病原体
We'll be able to harvest everything we need from his body.
你以为我让你派人马去盯着金·鲍尔干什么
Why do you think I had you put those operatives on Kim Bauer?
你们组织 仍需要证明杰克是活菌体
Your people are still going to need proof that Jack's viable.
派个生物学家在军事基地等我们
Have one of your biochemists meet us at the complex.
再次感谢你能赶来
Thank you again for coming.
皮尔斯探员
You can thank me, Agent Pierce,
你可以对我和盘托出  以表达对我的感激
By telling me what this is all about.
好  可是我们时间紧迫
All right, sir, but we don't have much time.
你暗示说这件事关系到奥利维亚·泰勒
You implied it had something to do with Olivia Taylor.
没错
Yes, sir.
几小时前
A few hours ago,
乔纳斯·霍奇斯在联调局总部外遇害
Jonas Hodges was killed outside FBI headquarters.
老天爷
My god.
当局相信他被害是因为
Now, authorities believe he was murdered to keep him
有人杀人灭口
From implicating others
以此保住牵扯进生化武器人物的秘密
Who were involved in the bioweapon attacks,
可我怀疑可能另有隐情
But I suspect there may be another scenario.
我有理由相信泰勒小姐
And I have reason to believe that Ms. Taylor
可能涉案
Might be involved.
真是骇人听闻的指控啊  皮尔斯探员
That is an outrageous accusation, Agent Pierce.
奥利维亚的确神通广大
Olivia is capable of many things,
-可我不相信她会杀人  -卡宁先生
- But I can't believe committing murder is one of them.- mr. kanin
请你听我把话说完
Please, just hear me out.
总统同意将霍奇斯
After the president agreed
列入证人保护计划后
To a witness protection deal for Hodges,
泰勒小姐对我说  她想要霍奇斯的命
Ms. Taylor made a comment to me about wanting to see Hodges dead.
是他害死了她弟弟
He was responsible for her brother's death.
她只是在泄愤而已
She was venting.
我也本这么以为
I thought so, too.
可后来她在办公室接见了一位老同事
Until she met in her office with an old colleague of hers,
名叫马丁·柯里尔
A man named Martin Collier.
我认识柯里尔
I know Collier.
那你应该知道他的作风
Then you know the sort of man he is.
对
I do.
可这也不能证明他们是共谋
But none of this constitutes proof of complicity.
对  先生  因此我需要您
No, sir. that's why I need you
登陆数字录音系统
To access the digital recording system.
看他们的谈话是否被录音
To see if their conversation was recorded.
你在唆使我闯入一间办公室
Agent, you're asking me to break into an office
而它已经不属于我
That's no longer mine.
然后进入代理联席幕僚长的分类录音系统
And access classified recordings of the acting chief of staff.
卡宁先生  如果我的怀疑没错
Mr. Kanin, if my suspicions prove correct,
你就会明白
You of all people understand
后果将不堪设想
How grave these consequences would be.
先生  泰勒小姐前几个小时的表现
Sir, Ms. Taylor's behavior
反常至极
Over the past several hours has been erratic at best.
现在她正在接受司法部调查
Now she's with the justice department investigators now.
我们时间紧迫
We don't have much time.
先生  请你快决定是否愿意协助我调查
Sir, I need you to decide if you're going to help me.
泰勒小姐  您能否再回顾下
If you could just again review the records
屏幕下的这段记录
On the screen below, Ms. Taylor.
我想确认这段时间内
I want to confirm that during the timeline in question,
除了你上传给我们的这份
You had no outside contact other than
反映在电话记录和网页浏览记录的活动
What's reflected in the phone and internet logs
你没有和外界接触过
You uploaded to us.
第三次声明  情况属实
For the third time-- that's correct.
我们只是为确保调查彻底
We're just trying to be thorough, ma'am.
我们已经占用了你足够的宝贵时间
I think we've taken up enough of your valuable time,
泰勒小姐
Ms. Taylor.
谢谢你配合我们工作
Thank you for, uh, indulging us.
不客气
You're welcome.
希望你们接下来的调查有所进展
Good luck with the rest of the investigation.
先生
Sir.
她来了
She's on her way.
泰勒小姐
Ms. Taylor.
我之前想找您谈话
I tried to get word to you,
可他们告诉我您不方便
But was told you were not to be disturbed.
找我说什么
Word to me about what?
请听我解释
Let me explain.
早啊  奥利维亚
Morning, olivia.
伊桑
Ethan.
你在这里做什么
What are you doing here?
我在收拾办公室时落了些文件
I'd forgotten some files when I cleared out my office, so...
特勤局非常好心  允许我近来
Secret service was kind enough to admit me
所以我可以取回文件
So I could retrieve them.
可以让我看看吗
May I see them?
也不是特别重要
Nothing terribly important.
但是我喜欢保存自己的所有备忘录
But I like to fully archive my memos for, uh...
留给我的后代们
Posterity, you understand.
你拿到想要的东西了
So you have what you came for.
是的
Um, I think so.
那么请你回避一下吧
Well, then if you'll excuse me.
好的
Of course.
皮尔斯探员
Agent Pierce,
你留一下
Stay a moment, please.
他来这干什么
What was he doing here?
怎么了
Ma'am?
卡宁
Kanin.
他在我办公室的时候你看着他没有
Did you observe him while he was in my office?
女士  有什么不对劲的吗
Is something wrong, ma'am?
是的
Yes.
是的  很不对劲
Yes, something is wrong!
任何人都不可以进到我的办公室
No one, and I mean no one, is to be allowed in my office
在没有
Without...
泰勒女士
Ms.Taylor.
要不要找人过来帮你
Could I get someone on staff to help you with that?
泰勒女士
Ms.Taylor...
保安
Security,
我是奥利维亚·泰勒
This is Olivia Taylor.
伊桑·卡宁正离开白宫
Ethan Kanin is on his way out of the white house,
将他拘捕
I want him taken into custody.
我到之前不要放他走
Detain him until I arrive.
女士  发生什么事
Ma'am, what's happened?
亚伦  他偷走了我的资产
He stole my property, Aaron.
卡宁先生
Mr. Kanin.
什么事
Yes?
先生  我们奉命要拘捕你
We have orders to detain you, sir.
谁下的命令
Orders from whom?
是现任联席参谋长
From the acting chief of staff, sir.
请跟我们走
Please come with us.
先生
Sir!
指挥中心  我是沃克
Command, this is Walker.
詹尼斯  收到请回答
Janice, do you read me?
收到  你没事吧
I'm here. Are you all right?
-是的  -发生什么事
- Yes.  - What is happening?
杰克劫持了运输车
Jack commandeered the transport.
他被迫帮助托尼逃跑
He was forced into helping Tony escape.
蕾妮  我是克罗伊
Renee, it's Chloe.
被迫是什么意思
What do you mean forced?
阿尔梅达的那伙人
The group Almeida's working for
威胁如果不合作就杀死金·鲍尔
Threatened to kill Kim Bauer if he didn't cooperate.
-他们抓到金了  -据杰克说
- They have Kim?  - According to Jack,
他们的人正与她一同在机场里
They have operatives with her now at the airport,
她自己可能还没有意识到
But I don't think she's aware of that.
-需要联络机场警察吗  -不
- Do you want me to contact airport PD?  - No.
在不清楚对方身份之前
We can't move on these people
我们不可以轻举妄动
Until we know who they are.
克罗伊  帮我直接连接到金所在的登机口
Chloe, I need you to patch me in directly to Kim's departure gate.
-她在7号登机口  -我这就开始
- She's at gate 7.  - I'm on it.
我来给白宫作简报
I'll brief the white house
告诉他们事情的进展
And let them know what's happened.
好的  我上路之后再联系你
Okay, I'll call you back when I'm on my way.
是的  这里是联邦调查局的紧急优先来电
Yes, I have a priority one emergency call from FBI.
请将我连接至7号登机口的探员
Please connect me with an agent at gate 7.
直飞洛杉矶的147号航班的乘客请注意
Attention, passengers for flight 147, nonstop to Los Angeles.
飞机维护工作已经完成
Maintenance crews have finished preparing the aircraft,
十分钟之后
And we should be ready to begin boarding
开始登机
In approximately ten minutes.
再次感谢您的耐心等候
Thank you again for your patience.
请以下候补机票的持有者
Would the following standby ticket holders,
到票务代理柜台报到
Please report to the ticket agent counter.
玛丽莎·波利
Marissa Boily,
金·鲍尔  罗伯特·莱顿
Kim bauer, Robert Leighton.
看来我赶上飞机了
Well, looks like I got on the flight.
我早说过嘛
Told you you would.
金·鲍尔
Kim Bauer?
-是的  -请到这里来
- Yeah.  - I'll take you over here.
好的
Okay.
有你的电话
A phone call for you.
喂
Hello?
金  我是蕾妮·沃克  仔细听好
Kim, this is Renee Walker. Listen carefully.
不要有太大反应  也不要四处张望
Try not to react and do not look around.
你现在很危险
You're in danger.
托尼·阿尔梅达派了人在监视你
You're being watched by operatives sent by Tony Almeida.
托尼  我不太明白
Tony? I don't understand.
他跟那些策划袭击的人有关
He's involved with the people responsible for the attacks.
我们拘捕了他  但他用你做筹码
We had him in custody, but he used you as leverage
逼你父亲帮他逃跑
To force your father to break him out.
我不相信托尼会做这样的事
I don't believe that Tony would do something like that.
金  他逃跑了
He's on the run, Kim.
还抓了你父亲当人质
He's taken your father hostage.
这件事你一定得相信我
You've got to trust me on this.
我正和一个小队赶往你那里
I'm on my way with a team to you now,
但是得先弄清楚谁在监视你
But we have to ID the people who are watching you.
他们是找到你父亲和托尼的唯一线索
They're our only lead to finding your father and Tony.
之前有个男人一直盯着我
There was a man that was staring at me earlier,
但是有一会儿没见着他了
But I haven't seen him in a while.
描述一下他的特征
Describe him.
他是西班牙人
Well, he was Hispanic,
中等身材
Uh, medium build,
棕色短发  身穿西服
He had short brown hair, he was wearing a suit.
那是弗兰克斯探员
That was agent Franks.
你父亲让我安排他去机场
Your father had me deploy him to the airport
确保你安全登机
To make sure you got on the plane safely.
他被跟踪你的人杀死了
He was killed by the people following you.
金  听着
Listen, Kim,
无论这些人是谁
Whoever these operatives are,
他们离你很近
They're in close proximity to you.
你父亲说他们发送了一个实时反馈
Your father told me they sent him a live feed
以证明你在他们视线内
To prove they had you in their sights.
你注意到有人拿相机或者手机吗
Have you noticed anyone with a camera or cell phone?
或者是笔记本电脑
Or a laptop.
什么
What?
我和一对夫妻说过话
There's a couple that I've been talking to,
他们就坐在我旁边
They're sitting right next to me.
那个男的有个笔记本电脑打开正对着我
The man has an open laptop right in front of me.
你能描述一下那个男的吗
Can you give me a description?
可以  他头发很长
Yeah, he's got long hair.
很高
He's tall...
-金  -我很感谢
- Kim? - Oh, well I appreciate that.
-好的  谢谢  -金  怎么了
- Okay, thank you. - Kim, what's wrong?
请转告行李处的
Please let baggage claim know
下次我会更小心的
That I will be much more careful next time.
金
Kim?
克罗伊
Chloe,
-你听到了吗  -我在
- Do you read me? - I'm here.
那些雇佣兵可能向金下手
The operatives may be moving on Kim.
通知机场警察  要他们不要轻举妄动
Alert airport police, have them lock down the terminal.
告诉机场保安正常巡逻
Tell airport security to maintain patrols.
别引起怀疑
Do nothing to arouse suspicion.
好的
Okay.
好的  再见
Okay, bye.
金  我们看见你在打电话
Kim, we saw you were on the phone.
以为你有麻烦了
We thought there might be a problem.
-需要帮忙吗  -不不
- Do you need some help? - No, no, no.
没有什么麻烦  我只是把电动牙刷
There's no problem. I just left my electric
忘记在行李箱了
Toothbrush on in my luggage.
-说他们弄坏了我的锁  -好吧
- That they broke my lock. - Nice.
你拿到登机牌了吗
Did you get your boarding pass?
拿到了  就在这里
Oh, yeah. It's right here.
她的行李安检时出了问题
There was, uh, a little security problem with her luggage.
我想他们再小心也不为过
I guess they can never be too careful.
你还好吧
You okay?
是的  我很好
Yeah. Yeah, I'm fine.
只是我第一次离开
This is the first time that I've been apart
我的女儿
From my little girl.
所以有些急着回到她身边
And I'm just a little anxious to get back to see her.
你们想看看她的相片吗
Would you like to see a picture of her?
当然
Sure.
我这里有一张
I've got one in here.
找到了
Here it is.
在哪  这张
Where is... yeah.
她叫泰莉
Her name's Teri.
她真可爱
She's adorable.
谢谢
Thank you.
那个是我的丈夫
That's my husband actually.
这个是
This is... ah...
干掉她
Take her.
不
No!
趴下  趴下
Get down! Get down!
都趴下
Everyone down!
二级警备  二级警备
Code two, code two!
疑犯持有武器
Suspects are armed!
趴下
Get down!
沃克
Walker.
我是金·鲍尔  保安都中枪了
It's Kim Bauer. Security's down.
-机场警察在哪里  -他们正赶去你那边
- Where are the airport police?! - They're mobilizing to you now.
那些雇佣兵怎么样了
What about the operatives?
那女的死了  男的正逃跑
The woman is dead. The man is getting away.
金  我们要通过他找到你父亲
Kim, we need him to find your father.
他朝那个方向走的
What direction is he headed?
沃克探员
Agent Walker?
见鬼
Damn it!
金  金
Kim? Kim?!
奥利维亚
Olivia.
我一直喜欢你这点  伊桑
I always liked that about you, Ethan.
就算是我小时候
Even when I was a little girl,
你也会在我进门时起立迎接
You always stood up when I came into the room.
恶习难改
Old habits die hard.
你从我的办公室带走了些东西
You removed something from my office.
我想要回来
I want it back.
我先前跟你说过  你随时可以拿回去
I told you before, you're welcome to them.
你非常清楚我不是在说那些文件
You know damn well I'm not talking about those files.
是吗
Do I?
伊桑  我发现那个电子录音机了
Ethan, I found the digital recorder.
现在把你拿走的还给我
Now give me what you took,
否则我会命令门外的安保警员
Or I'll order the security officers outside this door
对你进行光身检查
To strip search you.
好吧  我确实有录音
All right, I do have a recording.
不过是我过去在职那段时间的
It's a personal account of my last days
私人记录
In service to this administration
所以我觉得我有权拥有它
And I think I'm entitled to it.
没人有权利将敏感文件
No one is entitled to take sensitive material
带出白宫
Out of the White House.
那么你现在是在担心国家安全咯
Oh, now it's national security you're worried about?
事实上是的
As a matter of fact, yes.
我还保留着权限
Well, I still have my clearances.
为什么我们不在这里一起听这些录音呢
Why don't we listen to the recording together.
你现在没有职位来下达命令的  伊桑
You are in no position to dictate terms, Ethan.
你现在至少违反了10条联邦法条
You're in violation of at least ten federal laws.
你这么害怕的是什么  奥利维亚
What are you so afraid of, Olivia?
什么事有如此严重的指控
What's on there that's so incriminating?
我不是那个受到指控的人
I'm not the one facing incrimination.
你才是
You are.
但是如果你现在把录音交出来
But give me the recording right now
我会把那些指控都撤销
And I'll see to it that no charges are filed.
最后一次机会  伊桑
Last chance, Ethan.
在他身上找一个存储卡
Search him for a data card.
我被无故拘留
I'm being held without cause.
我要求和泰勒总统谈话
I demand to speak to president Taylor.
是总统阁下下达命令拘留你的
It was the president who ordered his detention.
如果是这样的话  我希望听她亲口说
If that's true, I want to hear it from her directly.
现在是犯罪事件
Well, this is a criminal matter now.
考虑到卡宁先生和总统阁下的私交
Considering her personal relationship
总统觉得介入调查
With Mr. Kanin, the president doesn't deem it appropriate
很不合适
To intrude on the investigation.
请站起来  卡宁先生
Please stand up, Mr. Kanin.
胳臂抬起来
Arms up.
你将铸成大错
You're making a terrible mistake.
泰勒女士这是严重越权行事
Ms. Taylor is grossly overstepping her authority.
探员  谢谢你
Thank you, agent.
把他带走
Process him out.
卡宁先生  请跟我来
Come with me, Mr. Kanin.
你根本就不明白
I don't think you understand
你所作所为的严重性
The seriousness of what you're doing.
我可不认为你就明白
I don't think you do.
霍布森探员  剩下几步路我来吧
Agent Hobson, I can take him the rest of the way.
好的
Fine.
皮尔斯探员  她肯定隐瞒了什么
She's definitely hiding something, agent Pierce.
还好我早就猜到了
Lucky for us I'm a paranoid son of a bitch.
我能问一下另一张数据卡是什么吗
May I ask what was on the other data card?
什么都没有  是空白的
Nothing. It's blank.
我可以拿到通讯办公室的进入许可
Well, I can try to get you into the communications office
以便你听录音
So you can listen to that.
太冒险了  也没那个必要
Too risky, and unnecessary.
我车里就有一台录音机的播放设备
I have a companion device to the recorder in my car.
听起来像是你一直在  期待这件事发生
It sounds like you were... expecting this.
和奥利维亚打交道是需要未雨绸缪的
One has to be prepared when you're dealing with Olivia.
我一有发现就通知你
I'll let you know what I find.
你们要干什么
What are you doing?
What are you doing?!
杰克  我们要利用你
We're gonna use you
来重新研制生化武器
To reconstitute the bioweapon, Jack.
脸朝下放在桌上
On the table facedown.
要花多长时间
How long till we know?
看情况吧
It depends.
什么情况
On what?
要根据他脊髓液里病原体的浓度来定
On the levels of pathogen in his spinal fluid.
给我一个大致时间
Give me a time frame.
15分钟
15 minutes.
好的  开始吧
Good. Get started.
托尼
Tony...
Tony!
-住手  -要先给他注射抗痉挛药物
- Don't! - Got to give him something to control the seizure.
让他一动不动的
I need him completely immobilized.
一知道鲍尔到底有没有用我会马上和组织联系
I'll contact the group as soon as we know if Bauer's viable.
没错  可我先要和你谈谈
Yeah, look, I need to talk to you first.
谈什么
What is it?
我想在组织里有更高的地位
I want a larger role in the organization.
而且我觉得现在是获得公认的最好时机
And I think this is a good time to make my case.
托尼  我们之前谈过的  是吧
Tony, we've gone over this before, okay?
这不合规定
It's not how it works.
你不能要求加入
You don't ask in.
只能是我们邀请你
You're invited in.
好吧  那帮我搞到一份邀请
All right, then get me an invitation.
听着  完成今天的任务后
Look, after what I've done today,
我认为那是我应得的
I think I've earned it.
你确实足智多谋
You have been resourceful, that's true.
但是
Still...
我知道你和上头直接联系
Look, I know you talk to the top guy.
我只是要你安排我们见一次面
All I'm asking is that you get us in the same room together.
我会毛遂自荐
I'll sell myself.
那不是个好方法
I don't think that would be the right approach.
-为什么不是  -因为他谨言慎行  托尼
- Why not? - Because he's careful to a fault, Tony.
而且他对他的匿名看的很重
And he's very protective of his anonymity.
我能理解
I can appreciate that.
但我也有底线
But the bottom line is,
没有我  就不会有这次行动
Without me, this operation never happens.
现在你能够影响他的决策
Now you have influence over him.
他相信你
He trusts you.
你可以说服他
You can convince him.
我以前见你做过
I've seen you do it before.
这次不同
This is different.
没错
That's right.
这次是不同
It is different.
这次是为了我
This time it's for me.
我准备好抽取脊髓液了
I'm ready to extract the spinal fluid.
按住他的头
Hold his head still.
马丁  我给你说  他知道了
He knows, Martin, I'm telling you.
不  奥利维亚  他不知道
No, Olivia, he doesn't.
最坏的情况会是  他产生了怀疑
Worst case, he has a suspicion.
我是说他根本没有时间
I mean he never actually had the time
去听那段录音
to listen to the recording.
是的
No.
好  而且他也没机会听了
Okay, and he never will,
因为你已经毁了数据卡  对吧
Because you destroyed the data card, right?
当然
Of course.
那么我们安全了  是吧
Then we're fine, all right?
只要你保持清晰的思路  别慌就行
So long as you keep thinking clearly and don't panic.
马丁  你忘了是我结束了他的职业生涯
You're forgetting I ended this man's career, Martin.
他不会错过扳倒我的任何机会  永远不会
He won't let me off the hook, ever.
你是总统的女儿  对吧
You're the president's daughter, okay?
相信我  在没有确凿证据前
Trust me, no one will come after you
没人会找你的麻烦
Without hard evidence.
尤其是伊桑·卡宁
Least of all Ethan Kanin.
奥利维亚
Olivia.
我得挂了
I've got to go.
总统在找你
The president's been looking for you.
-她要你马上去总统办公室  -发生什么事了
- She needs you in the oval office. - What's going on?
机场发现情况
There's a situation unfolding
牵涉到托尼·阿尔梅达
At the airport involving Tony Almeida.
马上要就此事开简报会了
We're about to be briefed,
-她想让你参加  -好的
- And she wants you in on it. - Okay.
一切还好吧
Everything all right?
是的  很好
Yes, fine.
在那边
Over here.
你看见他去哪边了吗
Did you see which way he went?
一片混乱  到处都有人在跑
It was chaos. There were people running everywhere.
詹尼斯  我是蕾妮
Janis, It's Renee.
说
Go ahead.
男嫌犯还在逃
The male operative remains at large.
金·鲍尔不见了
Kim Bauer is missing.
她不是去追他就是被挟持了
Either she went after him, or she's a hostage.
对所有通道发出优先警告
Issue a priority alert across all channels.
警官  我叫金·鲍尔
Officer, my name is Kim Bauer.
我正在追踪刚在航空集散站开枪的人
I'm following the man who shot up the terminal.
你得和调查局的蕾妮·沃克探员联系
You need to contact special agent Renee Walker with the FBI.
金  我是蕾妮  请讲
Kim, it's Renee. Go ahead.
我找到他了  他在南停车场车库
I've got him. he's in the south parking garage.
你现在是否看到他
Are you in visual contact?
没  他在我的楼上
No. He's on one of the upper levels
我在出口处
I'm at the exit.
收到  我们马上就到
Copy that. We're coming towards you.
快
Hurry!
坚持住  后援马上就到
Hang on! Help is on the way.
不
No!
金
Kim!
给你
Here.
你受伤了  我检查下你的手臂
You're hurt. Let me see your arm.
没事  听我说  蕾妮
No, listen to me, Renee.
那台笔记本上有摄像头
That laptop has the camera
他们用它来跟踪我
They were using to track me.
用的是D11反向路由器
With a D-11 inverse router,
我们也许能反追踪那个信号
We may be able to back trace the signal
从而找到绑架我爸爸的人
To the people that have my father.
我以前是反恐小组的系统分析员
I worked at CTU, systems analyst.
你们办公室有人可以帮我们吗
Is there anyone back at your office that can help us with this?
有  克罗伊?奥布赖恩
Yeah, I've got Chloe O'brian standing by.
和她通电话
Get her on the phone.
一旦你做了决定并一干到底
Once this happens, once it goes through,
就没有回头路可走了
You can never go back.
你后半生的日子恐怕就难过了
You will live with it for the rest of your life.
我不需要你们来给我训话
I don't need a lecture on conscience from you of all people.
我已认真考虑过此事
I have thought this through.
我不能忍受让那个畜生逍遥法外
What I can't live with is that monster getting away with this.
他必须为他所做的付出代价
He has to pay for what he did.
病毒含量比预期的要高
The virus load is even higher than we hoped for.
每单位脊髓液中含有十多个单位病毒
Ten-plus in spinal fluid alone.
不足以重组病毒
Not enough to reconstitute the pathogen, of course.
我们需要他的器官
We'll still need his organs for that.
他看起来不太好
He doesn't look too good.
他还能活多长时间
How much longer does he have?
几个小时吧  具体时间不能确定
A couple of hours, give or take.
如果他在我们提取病毒以前死了怎么办
And what happens if he dies before we extract the pathogen?
最好是能保证病毒携带者存活
Obviously, it's optimal to keep the host alive,
但病原体可以在他死后多存活两小时
But the pathogen could survive up to two hours after death,
或者更久
Sometimes even longer.
事实上  唯一除掉病毒的方法
In fact, the only sure way to destroy it
就是放在500摄氏度的高温环境中
Is by exposure to extreme
需要五百摄氏度以上的高温
Temperatures above 500-degrees celsius.
务必把那写在报告中
Make sure you put that in your report.
我会的  我已经发到你电脑上去了
I have, and I've already uploaded it to your computer.
很好  准备转移他
Good. Get him ready to move.
拿担架
Get the stretcher.
鲍尔有利用价值  但你需要保证相应设备
Bauer is viable, But you'll need to secure a facility.
那个好说
That won't be a problem
你一直都非常清楚
As long as you're absolutely certain
这方面我们会搞定的
That we can accomplish this.
我们已经啃下最硬的骨头了  艾伦
We've already done the hard part, Alan.
据我所知
And from what I understand,
有了适用的设备  纯血样提取
With the proper equipment, the actual extraction
以及人工器官移植就不成问题了
And bioengineering is fairly straightforward.
好的卡拉  我会和其他人联系  干得好
Okay, Cara, I'll contact the others. Good work.
他们要知道  该谢的还有阿尔梅达
They should know they have Almeida to thank for this.
是他意识到鲍尔是个问题解决途径
He's the one who realized Bauer was a possible source.
转达我的谢意
Relay my gratitude.
我认为你可以考虑更长远一些
I think you should consider going farther than that.
什么意思   你有何高见
Farther? What did you have in mind?
托尼和我们一条心
Tony believes in what we're doing.
他想担当更重要的角色
He wants to play a larger role.
听起来有点不靠谱
That sounds premature to me.
事实上  艾伦
The thing is, Alan,
如果我们不礼贤下士的话
If we don't make a significant gesture,
恐怕我们会失去他这个人才
I'm afraid we may lose him.
我甚至都不了解他  卡拉
I don't even know this man, Cara.
那么你就该去了解他
Then you should get to know him.
你该不会是建议我和他见面吧
Are you suggesting I meet with him?
听着  我强调的是
Look, all I'm saying is
他会成为组织里振臂一呼  应者云集的人物
That he would be a very useful voice in the mix.
他的实战经验弥补了
His field experience fills a knowledge gap,
我们计划中理论上的不足
In regards to our logistics and planning.
你这么说  是要大力保举他咯
Well, coming from you, That's a hell of a recommendation.
他就是不二人选了  艾伦
There's no one better, alan.
你不能像你查清组织里
And it's not as if you haven't vetted
其他每个成员的底子那样办
every other member of the group.
也许是时候该和他见个面了
Maybe it is time that he and I met.
我半小时之内到你那里
I could be there where you are in the next half hour.
你过来
You're coming here?
我认为这会是个好点子
I think it would be a good idea
如果由我亲自监督转移鲍尔的事
If I supervised Bauer's transfer myself;
我会让别人觉得轻松点  不是吗
Make the others feel at ease, don't you think?
但是拉卡  我要亲眼见下阿尔梅达
But, Cara, I'll look Almeida in the eye,
如果他有哪点让我看得不爽
And if, for any reason, I don't like what I see,
你清楚后果
You understand.
我不会让他活着离开
I can't let him walk out of that meeting alive.
我知道
I understand.
他想见你
He wants to meet you.
他一会就到
He'll be here in little while.
谢谢
Thank you.
一切看你自己表现了
It's up to you now.
把轮床推过来点
Wheel the gurney closer.
他太虚弱了走不了那么远
He's too weak to have gotten very far.
掩护南边出口  我去这边
Cover the north exit. I'll go this way.